I went over to Toru's place
for the first time yesterday.
Ooooh! So how'd it go with him?!
We didn't do anything like that, jeez.
But he's got like, a massive
TV mounted to the wall,
and loads of spare rooms on the
second and third floors of his house...
I thought he was a poor plebian like me!
S-Sorry to hear that...
What's up?
Shut it, you rich asshole!
--Wow, what the hell?
--You wanna order a cake?
Yeah, I forgot to pre-order one this year.
We should be able to handle it.
We don't take that many pre-orders,
so we're not swamped or anything.
What kind of cake do you want?
Ooh, can I get one with
tons of whipped cream?
Okay.
I invited Yuna-chan over for Christmas!
So we'll have you, Yuna-chan, Miyamura...
Wait, is he gonna be able to come?
You'd better invite him over.
Hell, I don't care if you can't make it,
but Miyamura better be here.
Sounds like you might be
sleeping in a manger on Christmas.
Christmas?
I'll probably be really busy helping
out at the shop from the 23rd on.
Y-Yeah, I figured.
Sorry. But if I get time,
I'll definitely come over!
It's okay, you don't have
to squeeze in time for me.
Once we eat dinner,
we're basically done anyway.
Sorry.
What?! You're not coming
for Christmas, Miyamura-kun?!
No, sorry. I already have lots of work
waiting for me at home today.
You're not coming for Christmas?!
Please come! Please!
S-Sorry, Sota...
Please!
I'm so sorry!
Bro!
Miyamura-kun!
Please, bro!
You know he's dating me, right?
Miyamura-kun!
Bro!
"Horimiya"
You know how up until recently,
I had a crush on Hori?
How recently?
I thought he gave up on her ages ago.
And you know how there was
the whole thing with Kono-san?
Why does he think "we know" this?
I have no idea what that
"whole thing" even was.
And Yoshikawa and I are
definitely more than just friends,
but I'm not gonna start
dating her or anything.
--What?
What?
I thought they were already dating.
See, I thought that's how you'd react!
I thought you thought
"I thought they were already dating"!
Stop thinking, you're gonna
give Iura-kun an aneurism!
You thought... we thought...
Look, we're not dating!
Well, okay, but...
don't you have a crush on her?
Hell yeah, I like her!
How are you not embarrassed
to admit that out loud?
I mean, do you guys think this is weird?
I don't think it's weird,
I'm just surprised.
But, like, shouldn't you be more
concerned about what she thinks of you,
rather than what we think of you?
If you two are happy with your
current relationship, then that's fine.
It's not my place to say
whether it's right or not.
Wait, what?
You're so cool, Sengoku-san!
Advice sure sounds different when
it's coming from a master romancer.
When was I ever a "master romancer"?!
Hey, there you are, Toru!
"Hitherto, and Forevermore"
Can I come by your place
to play video games today?
"Hitherto, and Forevermore"
I wanna finish the game we started before.
You do? Yeah, sure, you can come over.
Wait, no, not today.
Oh, why? You have plans already?
No, I don't have plans.
It's something else...
No, it's fine. You can come over.
Really? It's fine if
today's not a good day!
No, it's fine. It was gonna
happen sooner or later...
Sheesh, I never get used
to how huge your house is.
I'm home.
Why are you being so quiet?
C'mon, Yoshikawa,
let's get upstairs. C'mon, c'mon!
Huh?
C'mon, c'moooon!
Ugh, why is this hallway so long?!
Oh, maybe his mom or dad are home...
And he doesn't want me to meet them?
Sorry to rush you, Yoshikawa.
No, it's my fault.
I wish I were a hot guy.
What? Wait, why?!
What are you talking about?
I mean, if I were, you wouldn't...
W-Wait, why are you locking the door?
Huh? I mean...
Wh-Why are you loosening your tie?!
Huh?!
I mean, I always take
my tie off when I get home.
Yoshikawa--
There.
Huh?
I'm not gonna try anything weird with you,
but I don't want you to
be uncomfortable in here.
I have no idea what I did wrong.
I-It's not your fault!
I'm not uncomfortable
or scared or anything.
Oh, uh, is that right?
Yeah.
Oh.
Toru-kun?
Oh, no, I forgot!
--Huh?
--That's weird. Why are you
closing the door on me?
--Huh?
--That's weird. Why are you
closing the door on me?
Do you have a friend over?
Hey! Yeah, I do! Don't barge in!
Wait, is that your mom? Is she your mom?!
Oh, then let me get you two some drinks!
No thanks! We're good! Thank you!
She's blocking it with her foot.
Come now, don't be rude to your guest!
I can leave if I shouldn't be here, Toru!
No, you're good!
Stay right there, Yoshikawa!
Okay!
So her name's Yoshikawa-san, then?
Do you like cake?
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Let me go get you some.
I told you, we're good!
--But she's our guest!
--Wh-Who is she?
--And holy crap, she's tall!
--But she's our guest!
"Yashiro: 176 cm" "Ishikawa: 174 cm"
--And holy crap, she's tall!
--But she's our guest!
"Yashiro: 176 cm" "Ishikawa: 174 cm"
--And holy crap, she's tall!
I'll go get that for you.
Fine.
And don't barge in without knocking.
Weren't you gonna go get us some cake?!
Okay, okay. You're so impatient.
Is that your mom?
Thank God she's not. That's Yashiro-san.
She helps out around the house.
She always bombards me
with questions about you.
--Really?
--Like, "Who were you walking
with the other day?"
--Really?
--Like, "Who were you walking
with the other day?"
"Who's that girl you're
always inviting over?"
She's such a weirdo.
Who, me?
I told you to knock!
Oh, c'mon.
Which would you like,
shortcake or cheesecake?
Short... no, cheesecake.
Toru-kun, try anything funny,
and I'll tell your mother.
I'm not gonna try anything now
that I know you're here, Yashiro-san!
Holler if you need anything!
Yeah, yeah.
S-Sorry.
She's all excited 'cause
I brought a girl over.
She's nice, I swear.
Oh, okay.
I'm not gonna try anything now
that I know you're here, Yashiro-san!
"spin spin spin"
I'm not gonna try anything now
that I know you're here, Yashiro-san!
"spin spin spin"
S-So if she wasn't here,
he would have t-t-t-t--
"spin spin spin"
Yoshikawa?
Wait, what?! Something's
setting you off again!
What's up?
N-Nothing's up!
What?! Don't just stare at me!
"rub rub rub"
You're here to play video games, right?
Yeah!
I'm gonna beat it today!
Get it plugged in, Toru!
I'm happy with the way things are.
The cakes from this bakery
are great! Please, dig in!
"Iori Bakery"
The cakes from this bakery
are great! Please, dig in!
"Iori Bakery"
This is from Miyamura's shop.
"Student Council Room"
Oh, Sengoku-kun!
"JUMP"
Oh, hey, Remi.
Whoa!
What the hell, dude?
Sorry.
H-Hey...
You're coming over on Christmas, right?
Huh?
--On Christmas.
--Huh?
--You're coming over.
--Sen--
--Huh?
Can't you come over to my place?
I wanna hang in my room.
N-No, thanks...
Wow, Sengoku!
You made her cry!
You okay, Remi-chan?
That must've been shocking to hear.
Get 'im, Miyamura!
Knock some damn sense into him!
You got it!
"Still traumatized"
Hold on, let's hear why
he doesn't want to go.
You guys have no idea!
If you knew what it was like,
you'd understand!
I don't even wanna talk
about it, but here goes!
Come on in.
"INSECTS GALORE!"
--The mantis! The mantis
is gonna stare at me!
--Th-They're not mine! They're
my Dad's! I'll take them down!
--The mantis! The mantis
is gonna stare at me!
The... mantis?
You had your end-of-semester assembly
today, right? Did you get your grades?
"Kyoko Hori Semester Report Card"
Oh, wow, look! She's got A's
in everything except Art and P.E.!
Kyoko's a smarty-pants like her dad.
Well, I really hate to agree with you,
but yes, I suppose she does
take after you in math.
Why the weird preface?
This is such an emotional moment!
--Why?
--Hey, Yuri-chan, I asked you a question.
The next time you get your grades,
you'll be graduating!
--You failed tons of tests at
the start of your senior year.
--Oh, right.
--You failed tons of tests at
the start of your senior year.
--Starting this April, I won't be
in high school anymore.
--You failed tons of tests at
the start of your senior year.
--Starting this April, I won't be
in high school anymore.
--Your memory for petty details
is one thing I really dislike about you.
Look at mine, sis!
Wow, great job!
I wonder what I'll be doing
around this time next year.
After I graduate...
what will my life be like?
Hey, sis, are you looking?
Look at my grades!
--Wait, you just said we were both
good at math! Are you even listening?
--Are you listening to me?
--Wait, you just said we were both
good at math! Are you even listening?
Shut up!
Thank you very much!
That's a huge Christmas tree...
Watch where you're going,
or you'll trip and fall.
Oh, you're Yoshikawa-san's older sister!
You're not wearing your glasses today.
I actually just got contacts.
Oh, nice. I should think
about getting contacts.
Would you like me to buy you some?
What? Why?
Today is Christmas after all.
It's a little weird for a high-school kid
to buy a college student contacts.
You're wearing a suit today.
Yeah, I'm interviewing for jobs. It sucks.
Meanwhile, my dumbass sister
spends all her time screwing around.
You can laugh.
It's funny because it's true.
Go on, laugh. She's dumber
than a bag of rocks.
Oh, no, I meant...
Let's take a look...
Want me to go buy some dessert?
I'm good.
Get out of the way, dude!
How am I supposed to watch TV?!
The hell kind of tone is that?! I don't
care if you're my brother, you're dead!
And put your gross tissues
in the trash can, you dumbass!
I did! Kiko keeps taking them out!
Yeah, right!
Dammit, now it's over!
Keep your germs away from me!
"High School Exam Kanji"
"Middle School Math Review"
Yo, Moto, time for dinner.
Oh, okay.
Wow, look at all this food!
Sengoku-kun!
Come now, the bugs aren't that bad.
You're meeting Remi at
seven, right? It's 6:30 now.
You spending Christmas
by yourself, Sakura?
I do that every year! I'm Buddhist!
Guess I'll go.
Come on!
"SLUMP"
How am I supposed to eat dinner after
coming face-to-face with those bugs?!
You're not eating dinner with the bugs.
You're eating dinner with Remi.
Maybe I'll repeat a year and stay back.
Hurry up and graduate already, Koichi.
Really wish I could.
Wait for me. Just one year.
Just a year, mmkay?
I told you guys,
Miyamura's busy!
So? It's your job to
bring 'im over here anyways.
And what, ruin their Christmas sales?
Oh, he's gonna come
drop off our cake, though.
Whoa, really?!
Do you think he'll come in?
I dunno, he'll probably
stay at the front door.
Aww, that's too bad.
I-I'm not sad about it, if you're worried!
We're all sad about it.
"Miyamura belongs to everyone."
Um, Kyoko?
Oh, thanks.
"New text from: Miyamura"
It's from Miyamura!
Yay, Miyamura-kun's here!
Hello.
Let's play cards, bro!
Yeah!
Sorry, I can't stay at all.
Damn, your hands are freezing!
Get in here and warm up!
I'll get you a warm drink!
O-Okay, but I have to
leave right after I drink it.
Yay! Let's play Old Maid!
This is a whole lot
different from last year.
"One Hour Later"
"Exhausted"
I, uh... really have to go now.
Aww!
Don't "aww" him!
Sorry.
I'll walk him home.
No following!
You don't have to. It's so cold out.
I'm coming!
It's not that cold.
It's so quiet with all the snow.
Hori-san's gone quiet, too.
We're graduating soon, huh.
Soon? We've got a while, don't we?
You know, I...
I still don't know that
much about you, Miyamura.
There's tons I don't know.
Hori-san, I...
I don't know very much about you.
But I...
I want to be with you,
e-even after we graduate!
I-I mean, if that's okay.
P-Please say something.
Okay.
Let's get married!
Oh, God.
Okay, bye!
I'll make you happy!
What?!
I said, I'll make you happy, Miyamura!
Isn't the guy supposed
to say that to the girl?!
It doesn't make sense that way!
I'm self-centered, and all
I'm good at is studying and chores!
"crunch crunch"
I'm self-centered, and all
I'm good at is studying and chores!
"crunch crunch"
And I'm not nice to people, either!
Wait, what?!
So you can't be the one saying it!
I don't think that's
how it works, but okay.
I look forward to our future together.
Uh, yeah, same here.
"JUMP"
Right! Right! I'm coming--
Sorry, I gotta head back to the shop!
Oh, sure, good luck!
I'm freezing! I better get home, too!
My face is all hot.
"Next Time: I Would Gift You the Sky"
Do you go to the shrine
on New Year's every year?
I try to. How about you?
Only when it gets less crowded.
Wanna go together this year?
"shake shake"
"Fortune"
What's yours say?
"Keep calm and carry on," basically.
You sure that's it?
I mean, as long as you keep smiling,
I don't need much more.
What was that? I couldn't hear you.
Nothing.
Really?
I didn't say anything.
I'm happy as long as you're smiling, too.
So you did hear.
Hear what?
"Amazake"
It's kind of weird, you know?
You're the last person I see this year,
and the first person I see next year.
Yeah.
I hope it'll be like that
every year from now on.
Hey, Miyamura?
Will we be together forever?
Yup, together forever.
Forever.